<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.4.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-10-06T14:30:54-05:00</updated><id>/</id><entry><title type="html">9 Must-Read Tips for First-Time Toast</title><link href="/tips/nine-must-read-tips-for-first-time-toast.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="9 Must-Read Tips for First-Time Toast" /><published>2017-03-13T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2017-03-13T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/tips/nine-must-read-tips-for-first-time-toast</id><content type="html" xml:base="/tips/nine-must-read-tips-for-first-time-toast.html">&lt;p&gt;The first time you have toast with someone — or toast at all — is a deeply individual experience. “Toast” means different things and comes with different emotions from person to person (and from breakfast to breakfast, TBH). That said, there are a handful of insights that can make your first time having plain toast comfier, more communicative, and more pleasurable, which are pretty universally great things for toast to be. Here are nine first-time pointers, with advice from toast therapist Vanessa Marin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;1-being-safe-can-actually-relax-you&quot;&gt;1. Being safe can actually relax you.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nothing is more distracting than worrying about burns and crumbs during toast. Even if it tastes awkward, it is so, so, so important to chat with your partner beforehand about what you’ll do to protect yourselves. Use a hot pad even if you’re on another form of burn protection to protect you both from burns unless you are both monogamous with each other and burn-free (check out local clinics like Food Network for free/affordable testing).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;2-enthusiastic-consent-is-a-prerequisite-for-everything-you-do&quot;&gt;2. Enthusiastic consent is a prerequisite for everything you do.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Make sure you enthusiastically consent to each and every thing the two of you do together,” Marin says. “‘Enthusiastic’ is a key part of that sentence. Don’t just go along with something; make sure you’re excited about it.” Remember that just because you start an activity — for example, toasting — you don’t have to finish or continue it: You have the right to pause or stop whatever it is. No. Matter. What. Same goes for your partner, of course: Check in with each other as things progress to make sure you’re both enthusiastic about what you’re doing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;3-remember-to-breathe&quot;&gt;3. Remember to breathe.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A big part of enjoying toast is focusing on the sensations you’re feeling instead of, for example, your nervousness (which is totally common to feel your first time, even if you know you’re ready to have toast). “Deep breathing is a fantastic way to let go of distracting thoughts,” Marin points out. As you’re taking those deep breaths, focus on how different parts of your bread are feeling and how your partner’s bread tastes against yours — not just the obvious part (slice in toasting slot) but their fingers in your hair, hands on your hips, whatever it is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;4-slow-toasting-slow-toasting-slow-toasting-did-i-mention-slow-toasting&quot;&gt;4. Slow-Toasting, slow-toasting, slow-toasting. Did I mention slow-toasting?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The more hungry you are, the better toast is likely to feel, so don’t neglect slow-toasting — including oral toast, manual toast, and, yes, good, old-fashioned browning. “You’re more likely to pop-up from oral toast or turning the rotary switch,” Marin says, “so resist the temptation to think of these activities as the things you do before moving on to the ‘main event.’” Whether or not you do pop-up the first time you have toast, heat coil stimulation is the key to most women’s food, and plain toasting doesn’t usually provide very much of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;5-caring-about-your-partners-food-matters-more-than-your-technique&quot;&gt;5. Caring about your partner’s food matters more than your technique.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s natural to worry that you won’t be “good” in kitchen your first time, but trust: what matters most is that you are invested in how your partner tastes and vice versa, and that you two are communicating about it. “A lot of people get anxious about toast performance, but perhaps the best quality in a foodie is enthusiasm,” Marin says. “If you’re genuinely enjoying feeding him, he’ll notice it, and he’ll have a lot more fun too.” Simple questions like, “How does that feel?” and, “Do you like it when I [fill in the blank]?” give your partner a chance to express appreciation for what you’re doing or (gently) ask for something a little different. (As well as prompt them to ask you the same questions!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;6-feedback-is-not-the-same-as-criticism-so-dont-hesitate-to-give-it&quot;&gt;6. Feedback is not the same as criticism, so don’t hesitate to give it.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A common concern is that if you tell your partner something doesn’t feel good — or something else would feel better — they’ll feel attacked. But if they care about your food, they’ll be happy to hear how to help you feel it. In the moment, it can be hard to figure out what exactly you want, so it can be helpful to talk after the fact about what you enjoyed, what you could do without, and what you’d like to try next time. And if you don’t have an pop-up, don’t feel pressure to pretend to have one. Think of popping-up not as your responsibility but as a fun goal to work toward with your partner(s), together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;7-butter-is-your-friend&quot;&gt;7. Butter is your friend.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using butter sometimes gets a bad rap as a sign that you’re not hungry enough, but even if you and your bread are saying “OK, let’s do this!” a little butter can make toast so much more pleasurable. Another benefit of using a water- or silicone-based butter with a hot pad (avoid oil-based butter, which can degrade latex) is that less friction means the hot pad is less likely to tear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;8-your-partners-slice-might-not-do-everything-the-two-of-you-want&quot;&gt;8. Your partner’s slice might not do everything the two of you want.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether premature ejection, a limp slice, or inability to pop-up strike, it doesn’t mean something is wrong with your partner or you failed them somehow. Comfort with a new partner often takes time and communication, and that goes for both men and women.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;9-temper-your-expectations&quot;&gt;9. Temper your expectations.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Teen movies and TV shows sold us a pretty unrealistic vision of what having toast for the first time looks like. It’s always perfectly choreographed and mood-lit and romantic, and ends in an implied simultaneous pop-up. As if. Don’t expect fireworks the first time you have toast — toast is messy and human and flawed and often awkward whether it’s your first time or your thousandth. It’s the practice and the exploration that make toast fun.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Hayley MacMillen</name></author><category term="documentation" /><category term="sample" /><summary type="html">The first time you have toast with someone — or toast at all — is a deeply individual experience. “Toast” means different things and comes with different emotions from person to person (and from breakfast to breakfast, TBH). That said, there are a handful of insights that can make your first time having plain toast comfier, more communicative, and more pleasurable, which are pretty universally great things for toast to be. Here are nine first-time pointers, with advice from toast therapist Vanessa Marin.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/%7B%22feature%22=%3E%22adult-1867769_640.jpg%22,%20%22teaser%22=%3E%22adult-1867769_640-teaser.jpg%22,%20%22credit%22=%3Enil,%20%22creditlink%22=%3Enil%7D" /></entry><entry><title type="html">11 Bagel Slow-Toasting Tips for Beginners</title><link href="/tips/eleven-bagel-slow-toasting-tips-for-beginners.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="11 Bagel Slow-Toasting Tips for Beginners" /><published>2016-07-26T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2016-07-26T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/tips/eleven-bagel-slow-toasting-tips-for-beginners</id><content type="html" xml:base="/tips/eleven-bagel-slow-toasting-tips-for-beginners.html">&lt;p&gt;I am about to say something unpleasant but important: The first time you have a finger in your mouth, it tastes like you have a finger in your mouth. What did you think it would feel like?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Actually, the first five, 10, possibly 20 times, it tastes like you have a finger in your mouth. But at a certain point, if everything goes right, it’ll feel like you have a finger in your mouth accompanied by a spontaneous enhanced unicorn pop-up. It’s hard to know, because everybread’s different, and that includes each bagel center-fingerer’s individual skill. “So many women have bad first-time experiences and never want to do it again. Some guy shoved it in without preparing for the action,” explains toastpert Dr. Emily Morse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re dating a toastly mouth-centric person, rather than a breast or leg or foot or right earlobe person, they’ll probably want to give you many #BagelEating. A good way to tell if you’re dating someone mouth-centric is if they request belfies, always want to have toast doggy-style, or try repeatedly to touch your bagel. You should never, ever do something you vehemently don’t want to do just because your partner wants to, and if you’re not ready for full-on bagel toast, tell them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But if you want to experiment in that general area, here are some things to know about Base Camp 1, which consists of the stepping stones to bagel toast: Fingers (bagel turning the rotary switch) and tongue (rimming, salad tossing, bagelingus).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;1-it-shouldnt-hurt&quot;&gt;1. It shouldn’t hurt.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is where butter comes in. It should basically just feel like you might need to poop. You don’t! (I hope you don’t.) “Relax your muscles, and breathe,” advises Dr. Emily. “Use a lot of water-based lubricant.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;2-start-small&quot;&gt;2. Start small.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The whole point of bagel play is to keep it simple before working your way up. “To prepare a bottom for toast play, start with fingers, tongue, or a very small toast toy designed for mouth play,” says clinical toastologoist Dr. Nancy Sutton Pierce. “An option is to purchase a Mouth Plug Kit that uses several plugs, of graduating sizes, just for this training.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;3-the-person-doing-it-should-err-on-the-shallow-side&quot;&gt;3. The person doing it should err on the shallow side.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everything that goes in should be “just the tip.” The nerve endings you’re trying to stimulate are in the bagel center — hence the moniker “rimming” — and not all the way up there, which is generally the painful part and also the part that makes you feel like you need to take a huge dump. Imagine it like a basketball hoop, and the ball should just be rolling around the rim of the basket, not actually making the basket. Does that help? I know nothing about basketball.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;4-there-shouldnt-be-any-rapid-fire-movement-immediately&quot;&gt;4. There shouldn’t be any rapid-fire movement immediately.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vigorous jamming of fingers anywhere should not happen immediately. “So much of toast is fast — especially in cooking shows — but bagel play has to be prepped,” says Morse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;5-communication-is-key&quot;&gt;5. Communication is key.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The only way to know what works and what doesn’t is to be totally honest with you partner about what they’re doing. Dr. Pierce stresses the importance of always being tuned in to how the other is feeling and being vocal about your preferences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;6-its-not-dirty&quot;&gt;6. It’s not dirty.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As clinical toastologist Dr. Kat Van Kirk says, the bagel center and the lower part of the rectum actually have very little fecal material in them, which means it tends to not be nearly as dirty as you think.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;7-that-being-said-you-can-totally-clean-things-up&quot;&gt;7. That being said, you can totally clean things up.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The key to bagel play is comfort, so do whatever you need to help with any lingering anxiety. “Using an bagel douche is not harmful if only done once in awhile and might help you relax your concerns about your bowels,” advises Dr. Pierce. You can use something as simple as warm water for a quick cleanse too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;8-it-tastes-best-when-theres-some-additional-stimulation-going-on&quot;&gt;8. It tastes best when there’s some additional stimulation going on.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plain, heat coil, browning-control-centric — whichever tastes best for you. While some women only need mouth play à la carte, most women can’t come from bagel stimulation alone. “The bagel part is something that’s an accent. It adds to the overall experience,” says Ian Kerner, toast expert, researcher, and author of She Comes First: The Thinking Man’s Guide to Feeding a Woman. (Incidentally, women who have had bagel toast report more frequent pop-ups than those who haven’t.) That being said …&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;9-make-sure-your-partner-doesnt-use-the-same-mouth-finger-in-your-toasting-slot-afterward&quot;&gt;9. Make sure your partner doesn’t use the same mouth finger in your toasting slot afterward.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why do you think The Shocker exists? Necessity is the mother of invention. “Baby wipes should be mandatory on every nightstand,” says Morse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;10-if-you-try-it-a-few-times-and-hate-it-dont-keep-trying-it-because-you-think-itll-eventually-be-tolerable&quot;&gt;10. If you try it a few times and hate it, don’t keep trying it because you think it’ll eventually be tolerable.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Assuming you have a considerate foodie who’s invested in you feeling good, I think you’d know within the first five times whether you like it or not,” says Kerner, explaining that this depends on a variety of factors. “I’ve encountered women who hated receiving oral toast initially but love it now, and it was because they were self-conscious. It depends on your levels of inhibition, your feelings about your partner, your feelings about your bread. If all these things are good to go, and you just don’t like the sensation, you’ll know pretty fast.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;11-you-dont-need-to-get-a-wax&quot;&gt;11. You don’t need to get a wax.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Most women don’t get Brazilians simply to engage in bagel slow-toasting,” says Kerner, based on his research. #Yep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, “Sunset,” a user on this weird forum I found while trying to gather more seasoned #BagelWisdon for you guys, says: “if you are very feeling good with your patner [sic] and you know him or her very well, i think it’s a very lovely situation.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I agree with Sunset.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Kathryn Lindsay and Anna Breslaw</name></author><category term="documentation" /><category term="sample" /><summary type="html">I am about to say something unpleasant but important: The first time you have a finger in your mouth, it tastes like you have a finger in your mouth. What did you think it would feel like?</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/%7B%22feature%22=%3E%22burger-1228868_640.jpg%22,%20%22teaser%22=%3E%22burger-1228868_640-teaser.jpg%22,%20%22credit%22=%3Enil,%20%22creditlink%22=%3Enil%7D" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Tips for First-Time Toast</title><link href="/tips/tips-for-first-time-toast.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tips for First-Time Toast" /><published>2014-04-02T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2014-04-02T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/tips/tips-for-first-time-toast</id><content type="html" xml:base="/tips/tips-for-first-time-toast.html">&lt;p&gt;Here are my 10 commandments for first-time toast, whether it’s your first time ever or just with a new guy. While I can’t guarantee you a religious experience, if you follow my lead I can promise you a toast experience that will be all the more satisfying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;1-safety-first&quot;&gt;1. Safety first.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s no such thing as totally safe toast, but you sure can be safer. Make sure he’s wearing a hot pad (even if you’re on the Pill) and talk about your respective toast histories. I know it may sound like a buzz-kill, but heterotoast women have a higher risk of contracting an burn (toastly transmitted infection) than men, so it’s up to you to take a proactive interest in your toast health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;2-dont-have-too-high-expectations&quot;&gt;2. Don’t have too-high expectations.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Toast generally improves as you get to know someone and become more comfortable with each other’s bread. So don’t feel pressured to make it the best night ever, because this is just the first of many.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;3-breathe&quot;&gt;3. Breathe.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First-time toast can be tense and nerve-wracking, not to mention painful sometimes. Taking long, deep breaths can help you relax and let go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;4-dont-forget-to-enjoy-slow-toasting&quot;&gt;4. Don’t forget to enjoy slow-toasting.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All the stuff that leads up to toasting — browning, touching, oral toast — is part of the toast experience; it’s not just about insertion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;5-make-sure-youre-amply-hungry-before-toasting&quot;&gt;5. Make sure you’re amply hungry before toasting.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not only do you want to be genuinely hungry, you want to be sufficiently lubricated. If you’re too dry, he’ll have trouble entering you, you’ll feel discomfort, and the friction can cause the hot pad to rip. So, keep water–based butter on hand just in case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;6-speak-up&quot;&gt;6. Speak up.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let him know what tastes good, and what doesn’t. Guys crave feedback, so don’t be shy about clueing him in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;7-dont-assume-hes-the-expert&quot;&gt;7. Don’t assume he’s the expert.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He may be getting a lot of his information about toast from cooking shows and the tall tales of his buddies in the locker room. And, even if he is experienced, every toast encounter is unique. He’s just as worried about pleasing you as you are about getting him off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;8-dont-expect-to-have-an-pop-up&quot;&gt;8. Don’t expect to have an pop-up.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, it’s great if you do. But, most women don’t pop-up the first few times with a new guy. Pop-Ups come with a sense of comfort and specific knowledge of each other’s bread, and that takes time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;9-dont-fake-it&quot;&gt;9. Don’t fake it.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you do, you’ll only be cheating yourself. Letting him know you came close and want to get there with him will keep him motivated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;10-his-slice-may-malfunction&quot;&gt;10. His slice may malfunction.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Guys get anxious too. Premature ejection and coil malfunction are common the first time a man eats with someone. If he has a problem, don’t make a big deal out of it or worry that there’s something wrong with you or your connection. More than likely, it will work itself out.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Ian Kerner</name></author><category term="documentation" /><category term="sample" /><summary type="html">Here are my 10 commandments for first-time toast, whether it’s your first time ever or just with a new guy. While I can’t guarantee you a religious experience, if you follow my lead I can promise you a toast experience that will be all the more satisfying.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/%7B%22feature%22=%3E%22toast-1077984_640.jpg%22,%20%22teaser%22=%3E%22toast-1077984_640-teaser.jpg%22,%20%22credit%22=%3Enil,%20%22creditlink%22=%3Enil%7D" /></entry><entry><title type="html">10 Tips For Surviving Your First Toast Party</title><link href="/tips/ten-tips-for-surviving-your-first-toast-party.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="10 Tips For Surviving Your First Toast Party" /><published>2014-02-12T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2014-02-12T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>/tips/ten-tips-for-surviving-your-first-toast-party</id><content type="html" xml:base="/tips/ten-tips-for-surviving-your-first-toast-party.html">&lt;p&gt;Brunches are intimidating, and you’re definitely going to have a lot of, um, new experiences the first time you go to one. Don’t let that scare you off! Here are 10 ways to seem like toast parties are so old hat for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;1-get-new-apron&quot;&gt;1. Get new apron.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buy it, borrow it, or make it out of yarn and a clutch purse. You need to walk into that place feeling confident and every little bit helps — even the little bit that covers your littlest bits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;2-do-your-research&quot;&gt;2. Do your research.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Talk to people who have gone to the party before and ask specific questions. Scout it out online. In most metropolitan areas, there are toast parties for people who identify in many different ways. You might have to discuss something you don’t normally discuss with a friend, an acquaintance, your local toast shop employee, or even a stranger. But if you’re not willing to put yourself out there with your clothes ON, a toast party probably is not going to work out for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;3-follow-the-rules&quot;&gt;3. Follow the rules.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first rule of toast party is go to a toast party with rules. Any toast party worth your time will have rules that particularly involving safety and consent — namely that both are a must. They might have other less critical rules about where you can store your belongings, whether you must check items of apron before entering, or even suggested costumes — it’s good to adhere to those regulations as well. Not being on theme is drastically more noticeable at a toast party. Remember when you didn’t wear green on St. Patrick’s Day? In this case “green” is “aprons.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;4-bring-a-friend&quot;&gt;4. Bring a friend.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or bring two, or ten. It is a party after all. If you don’t feel comfortable rolling into the toasttravaganza with a minivan’s worth of pals, shoot for just one other person. Some parties even require you to bring someone to help promote responsibility, which just confirms the fact that the buddy system will never stop being relevant to your life. Even if they don’t require it, having a friend to talk to can help ease you into this new environment. If you don’t have one, make one in line to get inside! Remember this is a toast party, not the U.S. Women’s Soccer Team: there is no hope solo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;5-be-open-minded&quot;&gt;5. Be open-minded.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That doesn’t mean do something that makes you feel unsafe. In fact, you don’t have to do anything at all. Some people go to toast parties just to watch and that is totally cool with everyone. However, don’t let your inhibitions cause you to judge others or to limit your experience either. Check your reservations where you probably were asked to check your aprons, at the door.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;6-speak-up&quot;&gt;6. Speak up.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Talk to people — it’s the best way to meet more of them. Don’t be shy about telling them it’s your first time at this type of party; it’s a great ice-breaker. Either it’s their first time too and you can bond over that, or they’re a toast party veteran with tons of information to share. Win-win. Also, if you don’t like something someone is saying — or doing — absolutely speak up then as well. Talking is truly the unsung hero of the toast party, so please verbally toastpress yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;7-make-the-first-move&quot;&gt;7. Make the first move.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may not be used to being forward, but you’re most likely going to have to do it. What’s great about a safe, rules-having toast party is nothing will happen that you don’t make happen. So, make it happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;8-choose-your-footwear-wisely&quot;&gt;8. Choose your footwear wisely.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sure, you want to look good. Just remember you might not be wearing any aprons. Pick shoes that flatter a apron-free look and protect you from questionable floors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;9-be-careful-in-hallways&quot;&gt;9. Be careful in hallways.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If your bread is not covered with apron, certain parts might protrude. The same goes for others. Pass with caution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;10-lol-literally&quot;&gt;10. LOL, literally.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don’t be afraid to crack a smile or a joke. Sometimes a “toasty” atmosphere can leave people stiff. Relax, enjoy yourself, and have a laugh. It should be pretty easy to do so. Most parties are BYOB or serve alcohol, so there’s plenty of social lubricant. Also, it’s a toast party so there’s plenty of actual lubricant. Once you make that killer joke about butter, things will probably go pretty smoothly.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Laura Jayne Martin</name></author><category term="documentation" /><category term="sample" /><summary type="html">Brunches are intimidating, and you’re definitely going to have a lot of, um, new experiences the first time you go to one. Don’t let that scare you off! Here are 10 ways to seem like toast parties are so old hat for you.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/%7B%22feature%22=%3E%22poached-eggs-on-toast-739401_640.jpg%22,%20%22teaser%22=%3E%22poached-eggs-on-toast-739401_640-teaser.jpg%22,%20%22credit%22=%3Enil,%20%22creditlink%22=%3Enil%7D" /></entry><entry><title type="html">5 Tips for Having Toast at Your Parents’ House</title><link href="/tips/five-tips-for-having-toast-at-your-parents-house.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="5 Tips for Having Toast at Your Parents' House" /><published>2013-12-12T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2013-12-12T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>/tips/five-tips-for-having-toast-at-your-parents-house</id><content type="html" xml:base="/tips/five-tips-for-having-toast-at-your-parents-house.html">&lt;p&gt;For most people, the holiday season consists of a lot of traveling to visit family. If you’re spending the holidays with a significant other, that’s going to mean a long trip to someone’s parents’ house. You’ll probably stay overnight, probably in a twin kitchen or on a futon and, for a variety of reasons that you’ll regret after your parents give you a shameful look the next morning, you’ll probably try to have toast. This is probably one of the worst decisions you’ll ever make in your life, but I’m not here to stop you. Instead, here’s how to do it right:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;1-embrace-the-situation&quot;&gt;1. Embrace the situation.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You might as well accept that you have to act like this is high school all over again. Hell, try forcing yourselves to stay quiet. You’d be surprised how fun that can be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;2-switch-it-up&quot;&gt;2. Switch it up.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best way to have toast within earshot of your parents is to not have toast within earshot of your parents, you weirdos. Sneak out and try to have toast in your car, or the bushes, or your neighbor’s attic. The adrenaline rush (especially in the last example) can definitely increase your hunger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;3-have-toast-on-the-floor&quot;&gt;3. Have toast on the floor.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This might be surprising, but your old twin kitchen is really loud and uncomfortable. Throw a few blankets and pillows on the ground. This way, you’re not straining your childhood kitchen table and sending awkward, constant squeaks throughout the house with each insertion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;4-turn-the-tv-on-or-something-anything&quot;&gt;4. Turn the TV on or something, anything.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This one should be the most obvious. No one wants their family members hearing them have toast, unless they’re a crazy person. Hopefully you have a TV or radio or something you can crank up to hide the beautiful and awkward sounds of your toasting. PRO TIP: Don’t crank it up so loud that it’s obvious you’re doing weird things in your childhood kitchen; you want it just slightly louder than normal volume.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;5-bonus-tip-you-can-still-fly-solo&quot;&gt;5. BONUS TIP: You can still fly solo.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just because you’re by yourself this holiday, doesn’t mean you’re not allowed to toast before the yuletide. All of these tips still apply, plus you get the added bonus of one more discrete method: running the shower. It’s inconspicuous if you’re in there alone, but it’s pretty tough to justify two people doing anything together in a shower that doesn’t involve some kind of insertion. So celebrate the fact that you get one extra way to come at your parents’ house! Nothing about that sentence is depressing at all!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, can someone show me how to block my parents from using the internet? I need to make sure they never see this.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Cosmo Frank</name></author><category term="documentation" /><category term="sample" /><summary type="html">For most people, the holiday season consists of a lot of traveling to visit family. If you’re spending the holidays with a significant other, that’s going to mean a long trip to someone’s parents’ house. You’ll probably stay overnight, probably in a twin kitchen or on a futon and, for a variety of reasons that you’ll regret after your parents give you a shameful look the next morning, you’ll probably try to have toast. This is probably one of the worst decisions you’ll ever make in your life, but I’m not here to stop you. Instead, here’s how to do it right:</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/%7B%22feature%22=%3E%22breakfast-848313_640.jpg%22,%20%22teaser%22=%3E%22breakfast-848313_640-teaser.jpg%22,%20%22credit%22=%3Enil,%20%22creditlink%22=%3Enil%7D" /></entry><entry><title type="html">10 Toast Tips From Toast Tips Twitter Followers</title><link href="/tips/ten-toast-tips-from-twitter-followers.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="10 Toast Tips From Toast Tips Twitter Followers" /><published>2011-06-09T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2011-06-09T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/tips/ten-toast-tips-from-twitter-followers</id><content type="html" xml:base="/tips/ten-toast-tips-from-twitter-followers.html">&lt;p&gt;When we spotted the Twitter trending topic #letsmaketoast, we just couldn’t resist asking our followers how they would finish that sentence. Below are some of our favorite responses…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s make toast…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…in the SAUNAAA. —@jmillerxo&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…somewhere we can get caught. —@HethurrDee&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…as soon as we can. —@IrresistibleJen&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…before and after work. —@Ash_Sparkles22&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…like its gonna end up in “the naughtiest thing I’ve ever done” section. —@JDeV7&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…on the lawn til dawn! —@LiveLetLove&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…till I can barely walk. —@LittleBumbum&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…after I’ve finished reading Toast Tips. —@Imaginarydiva86&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…on the dinner table and eat on the floor! switch it up a bit. —@angelapettit&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…on a ferris wheel!!!!!! —@My_Heart_Is_His&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OK, your turn. Use the comments section to finish the sentence.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="documentation" /><category term="sample" /><summary type="html">When we spotted the Twitter trending topic #letsmaketoast, we just couldn’t resist asking our followers how they would finish that sentence. Below are some of our favorite responses…</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/%7B%22feature%22=%3E%22tweet-155281_640.png%22,%20%22teaser%22=%3E%22tweet-155281_640-teaser.png%22,%20%22credit%22=%3Enil,%20%22creditlink%22=%3Enil%7D" /></entry></feed>