<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>Toast Tips</title>
		<description>A handy guide to making loaf</description>
		<link></link>
		<atom:link href="/rss-feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>9 Must-Read Tips for First-Time Toast</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;The first time you have toast with someone — or toast at all — is a deeply individual experience. “Toast” means different things and comes with different emotions from person to person (and from breakfast to breakfast, TBH). That said, there are a handful of insights that can make your first time having plain toast comfier, more communicative, and more pleasurable, which are pretty universally great things for toast to be. Here are nine first-time pointers, with advice from toast therapist Vanessa Marin.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>/tips/nine-must-read-tips-for-first-time-toast.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/tips/nine-must-read-tips-for-first-time-toast.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>11 Bagel Slow-Toasting Tips for Beginners</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;I am about to say something unpleasant but important: The first time you have a finger in your mouth, it tastes like you have a finger in your mouth. What did you think it would feel like?&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>/tips/eleven-bagel-slow-toasting-tips-for-beginners.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/tips/eleven-bagel-slow-toasting-tips-for-beginners.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Tips for First-Time Toast</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;Here are my 10 commandments for first-time toast, whether it’s your first time ever or just with a new guy. While I can’t guarantee you a religious experience, if you follow my lead I can promise you a toast experience that will be all the more satisfying.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>/tips/tips-for-first-time-toast.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/tips/tips-for-first-time-toast.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>10 Tips For Surviving Your First Toast Party</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;Brunches are intimidating, and you’re definitely going to have a lot of, um, new experiences the first time you go to one. Don’t let that scare you off! Here are 10 ways to seem like toast parties are so old hat for you.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
				<link>/tips/ten-tips-for-surviving-your-first-toast-party.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/tips/ten-tips-for-surviving-your-first-toast-party.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>5 Tips for Having Toast at Your Parents' House</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;For most people, the holiday season consists of a lot of traveling to visit family. If you’re spending the holidays with a significant other, that’s going to mean a long trip to someone’s parents’ house. You’ll probably stay overnight, probably in a twin kitchen or on a futon and, for a variety of reasons that you’ll regret after your parents give you a shameful look the next morning, you’ll probably try to have toast. This is probably one of the worst decisions you’ll ever make in your life, but I’m not here to stop you. Instead, here’s how to do it right:&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
				<link>/tips/five-tips-for-having-toast-at-your-parents-house.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/tips/five-tips-for-having-toast-at-your-parents-house.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>10 Toast Tips From Toast Tips Twitter Followers</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;When we spotted the Twitter trending topic #letsmaketoast, we just couldn’t resist asking our followers how they would finish that sentence. Below are some of our favorite responses…&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>/tips/ten-toast-tips-from-twitter-followers.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/tips/ten-toast-tips-from-twitter-followers.html</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
